CURRICULUM VITAE

SUJIT SHANTARAM CHORGE JN-4, 13/13, SECTOR-10, VASHI NAVI MUMBAI - 400703.

E-mail: <u>sujit.c87@gmail.com</u>

Mobile No: 8655000124 / 9821598926



SUMMARY:

With 12+ years of experience in Brand Management, Product Marketing, Corporate Communication & Sales Support, I have successfully managed projects from Strategy to Execution and managed people ensuring efficient delegation along with their personal development. I am a creative mind with strategic skills and experience across varied industry verticals. I desire an assignment with an organization that will offer me growth opportunities and where I can leverage my present capabilities with a constant aim of achieving the goals & aspirations of the company & myself.

EDUCATION:

- MMS degree (Marketing) from Mumbai University.
- B.Com. Graduate from V.E.S. College, Mumbai.
- H.S.C. from SIES College, Maharashtra Board in the year 2005.
- S.S.C. from ST. Mary's School, Maharashtra Board in the year 2003.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

L&T FINANCE (NBFC registered with RBI)

Designation: Team Lead - Group Marketing

• Role: Product Marketing & Brand Management

• Business Type: B2B and B2C

• Job Location: Head Office, Kalina, Mumbai

• Period: September 2022 till date

• Job Description:

Responsible for Strategizing Product Marketing Campaigns:

Devising monthly & yearly strategies for promotion & visibility of key products namely Rural Finance, Two-Wheeler Finance, Housing Finance & SME Finance. Ensuring execution of planned campaigns through several suitable marketing mediums.

Brand Management & Brand Awareness:

Developing brand strategy & brand assets. Strategizing and implementing large-format brand awareness campaigns, participation in high impact properties like Cricket tournaments, Airport Activation & others.

BTL Activations & Events:

Responsible for planning and executing several industry & internal events for the organization and drive activities for Brand Visibility through BTL & ground-level activations and offering complete sales support. Devising & Driving sales incentive programs.

Digital, Content & Social Media Marketing:

Responsible for planning digital awareness, Influencer marketing & performance marketing campaigns along with the digital marketing team & agency and ensuring its effective execution. Generating suitable content for Social Media, Website, App.

Budget Management:

Planning, creating and tracking the marketing budget ensuring optimum utilization and timely vendor payments.

NEOGROWTH CREDIT PVT. LTD. (NBFC registered with RBI)

• **Designation:** Senior Manager - Marketing

• Role: Marketing Strategist & Lead for Brand Communication

• Business Type: B2B and B2C

• Job Location: Head Office, Lower Parel, Mumbai

• Period: September 2018 till date

• Job Description:

Responsible for Strategizing Branding & Marketing Campaigns:

Devising quarterly & yearly strategies for organizational branding & product marketing with overall budget management. Ensuring execution of planned campaigns for varied stakeholders through several suitable marketing mediums.

ATL, BTL & Events:

Responsible for planning and executing several industry & internal events for the organization and drive activities for Brand Visibility through ATL & ground-level reach through BTL activations and offering complete sales support. Devising & Driving sales incentive programs.

Digital & Social Media Marketing:

Responsible for planning digital awareness & performance marketing campaigns along with the digital marketing manager & agency and ensuring its effective execution. Generating content for the same and website management.

PR, Content & Internal Communications:

Content management, PR support activities, Newsletters and Internal communication for the organization.

Responsible for managing Partner Channel & diGibizz (A digital aggregator)

Managing Channel Partner association & engagement. A member of the founding committee of diGibizz; a digital aggregator and managing the overall platform.

NATIONAL SECURITIES DEPOSITORY LIMITED (Capital Market Depository)

• **Designation:** Assistant Manager – Marketing

• Business Type: B2B and B2C

• Job Location: Head Office, Lower Parel, Mumbai

Period: October 2015 to September 2018

• Job Description:

Responsible for Investor Education through several ATL/BTL activities:

Driving several awareness programs, seminars, business conclaves, events, exhibitions with an objective to spread financial literacy with respect to investment into capital markets amongst different set of target audience.

Website Management, Digital Marketing & Direct Marketing Campaigns:

Handle corporate website for regular updates and maintenance. Also, worked on conceptualization and development of NSDL's Investor Education platform to spread financial literacy.

Merchandizing and vendor management:

To suffice the gifting requirement of business divisions by sourcing and procuring attractive giveaway options for their customers and internal employees.

Internal communication/branding, PR, Creative & Content support:

Handling PR activities for several company events. Support in creating marketing collaterals viz, AV films, Print Ads, Brochures, etc. and internal/external branding as per the requirement for HO as well as other new & existing branches, by providing creative ideology and content for the same.

BASF INDIA LIMITED (Leading Chemical MNC)

• **Designation:** Executive – Marketing Communications

• Business Type: B2C

• **Job Location:** Head Office, Chandivali, Mumbai

• **Period:** October 2014 to September 2015

• Job Description:

Responsible for handling Events:

To co-ordinate, plan and organize customer events, product launch events, and inaugural events for several business divisions within the organization on local, regional and global scale. Also organize internal conferences and seminars for the company.

Responsible for handling Exhibitions / Trade Fairs:

To co-ordinate, plan and organize exhibitions / trade fairs for various business divisions on local, regional and global scale.

Support in creating collaterals like brochures, AV Films, Print Ads and internal branding for business teams as per their requirement

Merchandizing:

To suffice the gifting requirement of business divisions by sourcing and procuring attractive giveaway options for their customers and internal employees.

PR & Internal Communications:

Handled event specific PR activities and internal communications in terms of conducting employee welfare activities and also worked on internal newsletter.

MARATHON REALTY (Top Real Estate Group in Mumbai)

Designation: Executive - Marketing Communications

• Business Type: B2C

• Job Location: Head Office, Mulund, Mumbai

• Period: March 2013 to October 2014

Job Description:

Responsible for support in creation & execution of 360° media plans: Planning & executing ATL media involving TV, Print, Radio & OOH. Other Promotional activities, collateral stock production, executing onsite branding requirements, photoshoots & AV production; ensuring continuation of better customer site experience and upgradation in the same with the help of timely & effective competition study.

Planning & managing events & exhibitions at domestic & international scale:

Exhibitions - MCHI Property Expos, Sumansa Dubai Property Show and others External Events - Broker events, Launch events, BTL Promotional events Internal Events - Employee specific organizational events related to various departments like HR, Sales and others.

Planning and execution of Digital Marketing plans:

Planning and executing monthly plans for Digital Marketing based on project campaigns and timely enquiry report generation for the same.

BTL Promotional Events:

Responsible for planning and executing BTL promotional events viz: society, club, multiplex, mall activations ensuring lead generation and closure for the respective projects.

PR & Internal Communication:

Responsible for PR activities in terms of liasoning with PR agency for setting up interviews of senior management with various news channels and business newspapers and receiving media coverage for certain events.

VOLVO-EICHER COMMERCIAL VEHICLES LIMITED

- **Designation:** Business Associate Channel Sales
- Business Type: B2C
- Area Assigned: Mumbai, Thane & Raigad District
- Period: Aug 2012 to March 2013

• Job Description:

Handled a team of dealership executives to work together for the launch & establishment of a new product in the market

Responsible for product awareness in the market through various promotional activities like product demos, customer meets, channel partner and financer meets.

Responsible for meeting the sales targets assigned by the company for the product as well as for the dealership ensuring timely delivery of the product to the customer along with meeting their financing requirements.

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS & EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES:

AT JOB LEVEL:

Awarded for 'Best Integrated Marketing Campaign' at Pitch BFSI Marketing Summit Awarded for 'Best Multi-Channel Marketing Campaign' at Impact Digital Influencer Awards Awarded as Most Valuable Player in March 2021

Awarded as Employee of the Month in January 2020

Awarded for 'Best Marketing Campaign' at Global Excellence Marketing Awards

AT COLLEGE LEVEL:

Won Fashion Show contest at intercollegiate Level Won prizes in debate and essay writing competitions Won prizes in Carrom and Badminton competitions.

AT SOCIAL LEVEL:

Member of an NGO (Anamprem)

Delivering educational seminars on several topics in reputed social institutions

Recognized Emcee at varied social events

PERSONAL DETAILS:

NAME : Sujit Chorge

DOB, AGE : 24/06/1987 – 37 Years

SEX : Male

MARITAL STATUS : Married

NATIONALITY : Indian

RELIGION / CASTE : Hindu - Maratha

INTERESTS : Riding / Driving, Music, Sports.

DECLARATION:

Dear Employer,

This is in accordance to your requirement. I assure you the sincerity and respect to the designation that you would offer me. I do guarantee you that I will thoroughly understand and abide by the rules and regulations along with company's policies at any cost.

Sincerely, Kind Regards Sujit Chorge